Finding Aid for Detroit Urban League 1916-1992
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 1985 Accession
  - Photographs and Visual Images 1918-1985
    (Primarily 1950-1978) [see also oversize photographs, UBDm]
    In the course of processing this accession, the photographs from previous accessions have been reprocessed. All photos are now found in box 87. They are arranged, as much as possible, to accord with the organizing scheme laid out for the 1985 accession. That is, photos are linked to Executive Directors (Dancy and Kornegay) and to Departments (Education, Employment, Health, and Social Services). The Celebrations/Dinners, Guild, Green Pastures Camp, and individuals' photos lie outside this scheme. The small number of photographs from the 1992 accession have also been added to the photograph series in box 87.
    - Black Family Conference circa 1970s (Box 87)
    - Buildings
      - Mack Avenue Building
        - Exterior 1950s-1980s (Box 87)
        - Interior 1980s (Box 87)
      - Northlawn Avenue Building 1940s (Box 87)
      - Miscellaneous 1923-1970s (Box 87)
    - Celebrations/Dinners 1951-1985
      - 35th Anniversary 1951 (Box 87)
      - Annual Dinner 1954 (Box 87)
      - Dancy Retirement 1960 (Box 87)
      - 50th Anniversary 1966 (Box 87)
      - Distinguished Warriors 1980-1985 (Box 87)
      - Miscellaneous Award Ceremonies undated (Box 87)
    - Dancy, John C. circa 1943-1960, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Education 1940s-1972
      - General 1940s-1960s (Box 87)
      - Parents' Seminar 1962-1964 (Box 87)
      - Dancy-Twelfth Street Academy 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 87)
        (includes slides)
      - In School Street School Program circa 1982-1986 (and later?), 4 folders (Box 87)
    - Employment/Vocational Services
      - Equal Opportunity Day circa 1950s-1972, 3 folders (Box 87)
      - Jobs and Employment circa 1940s-1970, 4 folders (Box 87)
      - Job Development and Employment Institute 1966 (Box 87)
    - Green Pastures Camp 1931-1962 (Box 87)
    - Groups, Miscellaneous (Box 87)
    - Guild 1950s-1967 (Box 87)
    - Guild Gala 1964-1967 (Box 87)
    - Health Services 1940s-1975 (Box 87)
    - Historical (Box 87)
    - Individuals (includes Board of Directors and Award winners) 1940s-1970s, 4 folders (Box 87)
    - Kornegay, Francis A.
      - Portraits and addresses circa 1945-1978 (Box 87)
      - Awards, Ceremonies and Presentations circa 1946-1978
        - With 1 or 2 people (Box 87)
        - With 3 or 4 people (Box 87)
      - Dancy Library dedication 1964 (Box 87)
      - Dinners circa 1960-1978 (Box 87)
      - Working 1946-1975 (Box 87)
    - Miscellaneous (identified individuals in groups) 1940s-1960s (Box 87)
    - National Urban League Conferences 1918-1971 (Box 87)
    - Social Services 1940s-1969, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Staff 1946-1970 (Box 87)
    - Williams, Roy L. 1970s-1980s (Box 87)
    - Woods, Donald 1980s (Box 87)
    - Youth Activities 1945-1958 (Box 87)
  - Films, 1965-1975
    The Films series consists of several brief (15 to 30 second) clips and one film produced in cooperation with National Bank of Detroit title "The Bank is Open to You" which explores opportunities for African Americans in the banking industry. The film as been digitized and is available on DVD in the library or a flash streaming video on request.
    - Civil Rights 1968-1969, undated, 851100-1
      - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:15
        [Restricted]
      - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 1)
      - Streaming File: 851100-1, flash-flv
    - Civil Rights 1968-1969, undated, 851100-2
      - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:15
      - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 1)
      - Streaming File: 851100-2, flash-flv
    - Civil Rights 1968-1969, undated, 851100-3
      - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:15
      - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 1)
      - Streaming File: 851100-3, flash-flv
    - Civil Rights, 1968-1969, 851100-4
      - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:00:20
      - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 1)
      - Streaming File: 851100-4, flash-flv
    - NBD's "The Bank is Open to You" 1965, 851100-5
      - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, optical, 00:15:00
      - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 1)
      - Streaming File: 851100-5, flash-flv
- 1992 Accession 1924-1992, 1978-1992
  (Boxes 88-96)
  1992 accession of 9 linear feet of records documents principally the activities of the Detroit Urban League in the 1980s. There is, however, significant material from the 1970s and a small amount from the 1960s and earlier. The 1992 accession of the Detroit Urban League materials is divided into five series: the Executive Director's/President's file, 1961-1992; the Deputy Director's file, 1968-1978; Staff Files, 1978-1992; and Printed Material, 1974-1991. It must be noted that very few sequences in this accession are complete.
  - Executive Director's Files
    The Executive Director's/President's file is continued from earlier accessions. Due to a change in the organizational structure in 1978, the title of executive director was now changed to president. There are five sub-series in this series: Executive Director Francis A. Kornegay, 1960-1978; President Roy Levy Williams, 1978-1984; Interim President Sue Hamilton-Smith, 1984-1985; President Donald W. Woods, 1985-1987; and President N. Charles Anderson, 1987-.
    - Kornegay, Francis A. 1960-1978
      The Kornegay subseries is relatively small (the majority of his papers and records are found in earlier D.U.L. accessions and in the Francis A. Kornegay collection), mostly reflecting his later years as Executive Director. However, there are some materials from the early 1960s, including information on the Religious Resources Committee (1962-1963). Of particular interest in this sequence are the records from the Public Issues Task Force.
      - Bibliography -- Afro-American History circa 1967 (Box 88)
      - Booz, Allen and Hamilton Report (Comments on the) 1975 (Box 88)
      - Budget 1978 (Box 88)
      - Community Action for Detroit's Youth 1962, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Community Planning for Community Schools circa 1962 (Box 88)
      - Correspondence circa 1971 and 1976-1978 (Box 88)
      - Detroit Institute of Technology 1978, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Detroit Police Department -- Revised Report on the Employment Practices 1963 (Box 88)
      - Education Task Force 1976-1978 (Box 88)
      - Emancipation Proclamation Centennial 1963 (Box 88)
      - History of D.U.L. circa 1964 (Box 88)
      - Internal Revenue Service 1977 (Box 88)
      - Michigan Employment Security Commission 1962 (Box 88)
      - Michigan Welfare League 1962 (Box 88)
      - Miscellaneous 1966 (Box 88)
      - National Urban League -- Terms of Affiliation for Urban League Affiliates 1972 (Box 88)
      - Parents Seminar Report 1963 (Box 88)
      - Press Releases 1970-1975 (Box 88)
      - Project F.A.S.T. 1966 (Box 88)
      - Public Issues Task Force 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Public Issues Task Force -- Advertisement Campaign 1976-1977 (Box 88)
      - Race Questionnaire circa 1960 (Box 88)
      - Ralston Purina Summer Project 1977-1978 (Box 88)
      - Religious Resources Committee 1962-1963, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Resumes 1975-78 (Box 88)
      - Sears Closing 1978 (Box 88)
      - Scholarship Committee circa 1954 (Box 88)
      - Staff Meetings (General) 1973-1978 (Box 88)
      - State Income Tax for Education (Proposed Project for D.U.L.) 1966 (Box 88)
      - A Tribute to Dr. Francis A. Kornegay, President D.U.L. 1978 (Box 88)
      - United Negro College Fund (Saginaw, Mich) 1978 (Box 88)
      - Vocational Services Department
        - General 1971-1977 (Box 88)
        - Annual Report 1961 (Box 88)
        - Detroit Market Survey 1975 (Box 88)
      - Youth in Correctional Institutions -- Research Data 1976-1977 (Box 88)
  - President's Files
    - Williams, Roy Levy 1978-1984
      The Roy Levy Williams subseries represents the core of the president's file. Adding and rejuvenating programs, Williams continued the work of the League. He increased the scope of membership drives, created the Blue Monday Network of young minority professionals as mentors, and created the Distinguished Warriors Annual Award Dinner (at first calling it the Old Warriors Award).
      - Affirmative Action Policies and Statements circa 1982 (Box 88)
      - "Black Students in Higher Education" 1983 (Box 88)
      - Board of Directors 1978-1982, 12 folders (Box 88)
      - Board of Directors 1983-1984, 7 folders (Box 89)
      - Booz-Allen 1979 (Box 89)
      - Brush Park Citizens District Council 1984 (Box 89)
      - Brush Park Citizens District Council -- Board Manual circa 1974 (Box 89)
      - Budget 1980-1984, 5 folders (Box 89)
      - Building Repair Grants 1981-1984 (Box 89)
      - Butzel-Stevens-Pope Scholarship 1979-1983 (Box 89)
      - Census 1980 (Box 89)
      - Child Care Food Program 1984-1985 (Box 89)
      - Chrysler 1984 (Box 89)
      - Community and Leadership Development 1980 (Box 89)
      - Community and Leadership Development -- Senior Citizens Taxicab Transport Project to Banks 1979 (Box 89)
      - Community Relations -- U.S. Army 1980 (Box 89)
      - Community Services Task Force circa 1983 (Box 89)
      - Dancy Street Academy 1979 (Box 89)
      - Detroit Institute of Technology 1979-1981 (Box 89)
      - Distinguished Warriors 1980-1984 (Box 89)
      - Education Task Force 1979-1984, 5 folders (Box 89)
      - Educational Street Work and Parental Involvement Project 1981 (Box 89)
      - Employment Task Force 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 89)
      - Equal Opportunity Program (Metro-Detroit) 1982 (Box 89)
      - Executive Cabinet Meetings circa 1983 (Box 89)
      - Facilities -- Linwood Building 1980 (Box 89)
      - Fleming, Willie J. -- Commendation 1982 (Box 89)
      - Grand Valley State Colleges -- Detroit Regional Center 1980 (Box 89)
      - Homework Hotline 1982 (Box 89)
      - History of D.U.L. circa 1982-1984 (Box 89)
      - Hypertension Project 1980 (Box 89)
      - Joy Middle School 1984 (Box 89)
      - "Legal Responsibility and Accountability of Agency Trustees" (paper) 1983 (Box 89)
      - Lobby Registration Act 1984 (Box 89)
      - Louis, Joe 1982 (Box 89)
      - Membership 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 89)
      - National Urban Education Association 1979 (Box 89)
      - National Urban Fellows 1980 (Box 89)
      - National Urban League
        - 1980-1984, 3 folders (Box 89)
        - Affiliate Reporting Requirements 1984 (Box 89)
        - Allocation of Costs 1978 (Box 89)
        - Central Regional Office 1984 (Box 89)
        - Convention on WTVS (Channel 56) 1982 (Box 89)
        - Educational Surveys circa 1984 (Box 89)
        - Expanded Orientation for New CEOs 1984 (Box 89)
        - Minorities and Crime and the Administration of Justice 1980 (Box 89)
        - Office of Program Development and Training 1980 (Box 89)
        - Operation Big Vote 1980 (Box 90)
      - Neighborhood Opportunity Program 1981-1982 (Box 90)
      - Neighborhood Service Organization 1984 (Box 90)
      - New Thrust circa 1979 (Box 90)
      - On the Job Training Project (OJT) 1978-1980 (Box 90)
      - Personnel
        - 1978-1984 (Box 90)
        - Terry [Lee] Alexander 1977-1984 (Box 90)
        - Terry Alexander--Correspondence and Memos 1977-1979 (Box 90)
        - Karen Brantley 1979 (Box 90)
        - Leatrice Eagleson 1980 (Box 90)
        - Annette Seaborn 1980 (Box 90)
        - Larry L. Simmons 1982 (Box 90)
        - Roy Levy Williams 1978-1984 (Box 90)
      - Peter Claver Neighborhood Services Barrier Free and Renovation Project 1979 (Box 90)
      - Planning 1983 (Box 90)
      - Program Summary 1983 (Box 90)
      - Project Redirection 1980, 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Prospectus 1984 (Box 90)
      - Public Issues Task Force 1978-1984, 5 folders (Box 90)
      - Radisson-Cadillac Hotel 1980 (Box 90)
      - Racism and the Media 1980 (Box 90)
      - Rape 1984 (Box 90)
      - Recreation and Cultural Program 1979 (Box 90)
      - Republican Party 1981-1983 (Box 90)
      - Resumes 1978-1980 (Box 90)
      - The Rhythm and the Blues (fund raiser) 1894 (Box 90)
      - Samaritan Health Center 1979 (Box 90)
      - Save-A-Person Detoxification Residential Treatment Center 1982 (Box 90)
      - School Desegregation Workshop Notes circa 1978-1984 (Box 90)
      - Search Committee 1984 (Box 90)
      - Seat Belt Safety 1981 (Box 90)
      - SEMCOG 1983 (Box 90)
      - Service Forecast 1980 (Box 90)
      - Shaw College at Detroit 1979-1982 (Box 90)
      - Simmons, Richard Jr. 1980-1982 (Box 90)
      - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC) 1981-1982 (Box 90)
      - Speed Letters 1978-1984 (Box 90)
      - Street Academies 1980 (Box 90)
      - Street Chariot 1980 (Box 90)
      - Strohs 1983 (Box 90)
      - Summer Occupational Awareness Program (SOAP) 1980 (Box 90)
      - Summer Youth Employment Program 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Tax Exempt Shelters for Schools 1982 (Box 90)
      - Taylor, Ross 1981 (Box 90)
      - United Foundation Budget Presentation 1983 (Box 90)
      - United Foundation Program Review (Response to the) 1984 (Box 90)
      - United Community Services -- Correspondence 1979 (Box 90)
      - U.S. Department of Housing and Development 1979-1980 (Box 90)
      - Urban Alliance 1980 (Box 90)
      - Urban Initiatives Anti-Crime Program 1979 (Box 90)
      - Urban League Briefs 1979-1980 (Box 90)
      - Voter Registration Drive 1984 (Box 90)
      - Williams, Roy Levy
        - Correspondence--Acknowledgments 1984 (Box 90)
        - Correspondence 1981-1984 (Box 90)
        - Personal 1978-1984 (Box 90)
        - Personal Correspondence 1978-1984 (Box 90)
        - Response to Correspondence 1981-1984 (Box 90)
        - Speeches 1978-1982 (Box 90)
        - Vote "Yes" Detroit Committee 1981 (Box 90)
      - Workshop Training circa 1978-1984 (Box 90)
      - Youth Development Center [In-School Street Academy/Services (IS3)] 1979-1984 (Box 90)
    - Hamilton-Smith, Sue 1984-1985
      The Sue Hamilton-Smith subseries, though small in size, complements the records she created while she was Executive Assistant to the President and Vice-President for External Affairs. Hamilton-Smith served as Interim President of the D.U.L. during the search which resulted in Donald W. Woods becoming president of the D.U.L.
      - Board of Directors 1984-1985, 3 folders (Box 91)
      - Budget 1985 (Box 91)
      - Child Abuse Prevention Federal Challenge Grants Program 1985 (Box 91)
      - Community Development and Economic Development Committee 1985 (Box 91)
      - Detroit City Council -- D.U.L. Testimony 1985 (Box 91)
      - Executive Committee 1985 (Box 91)
      - Financial Statements 1985 (Box 91)
      - Michigan Occupational Information System (MOIS) 1985 (Box 91)
      - Memos and Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 91)
      - Minority and Female Owned Businesses (Mich.) 1985 (Box 91)
      - National Urban League 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Personnel
        - 1984 (Box 91)
        - Alfred Bryant 1984 (Box 91)
        - Barbara Rennie 1985 (Box 91)
      - Quarterly Report (3rd Quarter) 1984 (Box 91)
      - Quarterly Report (4th Quarter) 1985 (Box 91)
      - Youth Development Committee 1985 (Box 91)
    - Woods, Donald W. 1985-1987
      Woods served only two years as president of the D.U.L. His small collection of papers displays his relationship with the D.U.L. Board of Directors, his emphasis on work with young urban people and his drive to increase the League's membership and profile in the Detroit community.
      - Board of Directors 1985-1987, 4 folders (Box 91)
      - Budget 1987 (Box 91)
      - Correspondence 1985-1986 (Box 91)
      - Distinguished Warriors 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Executive Committee 1985-1986 (Box 91)
      - Facilities Committee 1987 (Box 91)
      - Joy Middle School 1985 (Box 91)
      - Membership Drive circa 1985-1987 (Box 91)
      - National Urban League 1985 (Box 91)
      - Personnel -- Lea[trice] Eagleson 1985 (Box 91)
      - Press Release: The D.U.L. Supports School Based Clinics 1986 (Box 91)
      - Research 1986 (Box 91)
      - The State of Black Michigan: 1985. -- Clippings 1985 (Box 91)
      - Strategic Plan 1986-1987 (Box 91)
      - United Foundation -- Correspondence 1986 (Box 91)
      - "You Can Change a Life" circa 1985 (Box 91)
    - Anderson, N. Charles 1987-
      N. Charles Anderson's series contains information about the N.U.L. convention in Detroit in 1988. In 1992, Anderson continues his work at the Urban League.
      - Board of Directors 1987-1992, 4 folders (Box 91)
      - Detroit Alliance for Youth Services 1988 (Box 91)
      - Financial 1987 (Box 91)
      - Job Descriptions (Staff and Volunteer) 1988 (Box 91)
      - National Urban League Convention -- The Michigan Chronicle July 30, 1988 (Box 91)
      - National Urban League -- Correspondence 1989 (Box 91)
      - Project Empowerment 1990 (Box 91)
      - Staff circa 1988 (Box 91)
    - Undated President's File, 2 folders
      - D.U.L. Guild undated (Box 91)
      - Job Description -- Vice-President undated (Box 91)
  - Deputy Director's Files
    Winston Lang, a social worker, came to work for the D.U.L. in the late 1960s. He soon became Deputy Director, Kornegay's assistant (in 1970). This material chiefly contains budget and funding records from 1968-1978 and correspondence. Although there are similar folders in earlier accessions, there is very little duplication of information in this series.
    - Lang, Winstonia [A.] 1968-1978
      - Budget 1968-1976, 10 folders (Box 91)
      - Budget 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 92)
      - "Confidentiality of Information Obtained from Clients." circa 1971 (Box 92)
      - Correspondence (primarily of Kornegay) 1970-1972, 14 folders (Box 92)
      - Financial and Personnel Report 1971 (Box 92)
      - Memos 1970-1973 (Box 92)
      - News Releases 1971-1975 (Box 92)
      - Staff 1975 (Box 92)
  - Staff Files 1974-1989
    The staff files series contains four subseries created by officers of the Urban League: Sue Hamilton-Smith, 1978-1984; Barbara Rennie, 1982-1988 and 1974-87; Annette Seaborn, 1985-1988; and Jo-Anne Woodard, 1985-1988. The subseries of the staff files are arranged chronologically by the date when an individual began working at the D.U.L. With the exception of Barbara Rennie's Report File, 1974-1987, which is a chronological file, all of these subseries are alphabetically arranged topical files.
    - Hamilton-Smith, Sue 1978-1984
      Sue Hamilton-Smith came in 1979 to work for the Urban League. She had previously served on its Public Issues Task Force and had worked with Williams when he was an assistant to Governor Milliken. The Sue Hamilton-Smith subseries contains material on League programs during her tenure as Executive Assistant to the President and Vice-President for External Affairs.
      - Albert Kahn House -- Application for National Register of Historic Places 1972-1975 (Box 92)
      - Butzel-Stevens-Pope Scholarship Fund 1974 (Box 92)
      - Education and Youth Task Force 1983-1984 (Box 92)
      - Guild Workshop 1981 (Box 92)
      - In-School Street School (IS3) 1982-1985 (Box 92)
      - "Jobless Inner City Youth vs. The Rest of America: The Birth of a Separate Values System" 1981 (Box 92)
      - National Conference on Social Welfare 1980 (Box 92)
      - National Urban League 1980 (Box 92)
      - Project Redirection 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Special Fund Balances 1973-1974 (Box 92)
      - Summer Youth Employment Project 1981-1982, 3 folders (Box 92)
      - Combined Services Project II-B 1981, 17 folders (Box 92)
    - Renne, Barbara 1982-1988
      Barbara Rennie was a research specialist for the D.U.L., collecting and conducting research on urban populations, especially in Detroit. Rennie also wrote position and research papers for the D.U.L. Additionally, she was responsible for statistical reports to the Board of Directors and United Community Services of Detroit. She worked to improve and restructure the D.U.L.'s relationship with the United Way (formerly the United Foundation) and United Community Services of Detroit by submitting statistically correct reports on time and properly formatted to the agencies.
      - Topical File
        - Addiction Research Institute 1986 (Box 92)
        - Albert Kahn House
          - General 1983-1987 (Box 92)
          - Neighborhood Opportunity Fund (NOF) Grant Application 1983 (Box 92)
          - Preservation and Conservation 1976-1986 (Box 92)
        - Articles of Association 1924 (Box 93)
        - Basic Educational Skills Tutorial (B.E.S.T.) 1984 (Box 93)
        - Black Families -- Coalition for Strengthening the Black Family 1986 (Box 93)
        - Black Youth 1983-1985 (Box 93)
        - Blue Monday Network 1983 (Box 93)
        - Brush Park 1980-1986, 3 folders (Box 93)
        - Budget 1983-1987, 7 folders (Box 93)
        - Cabinet Meeting 1987 (Box 93)
        - Cable Vision Bids 1983 (Box 93)
        - Civil Rights 1983-1985 (Box 93)
        - Clippings 1985-1986 (Box 93)
        - Committee Assignments 1983-1984 (Box 93)
        - Committees 1987 (Box 93)
        - Community Files (Census Statistics) 1984 (Box 93)
        - Community Services Block Grant (CSBG) 1984-1985 (Box 93)
        - Community Services Task Force 1983 (Box 93)
        - Coordinating Council on Human Relations 1981-1985 (Box 93)
        - Correspondence 1983-1986 (Box 93)
        - Counseling (Individual and Group) 1984-1985 (Box 93)
        - Demographic Description of Areas within the Immediate Proximity of Urban League Facilities 1980 (Box 93)
        - Detroit City 1983 (Box 93)
        - Detroit Test Data 1983 (Box 93)
        - Distinguished Warriors 1987-1988 (Box 93)
        - Education Initiatives circa 1985-1987 (Box 93)
        - Executive Cabinet Meeting Minutes February-May, 1983 (Box 93)
        - Executive Committee 1987 (Box 93)
        - Facilities
          - General 1956-1958 (Box 93)
          - Linwood Renovation 1986 (Box 93)
        - General Motors 1984 (Box 93)
        - History and Background of D.U.L. 1981 (Box 93)
        - History of D.U.L. -- Slide Presentation Transcript 1984 (Box 93)
        - In-School Street Program (IS3) 1982-1985 (Box 93)
        - Information Sheets circa 1983 (Box 93)
        - Insurance and Property 1985 (Box 93)
        - Interns 1983 (Box 93)
        - Joy Middle School 1983-1984 (Box 93)
        - Kornegay, Francis A. circa 1975 (Box 93)
        - LENS International 1986 (Box 93)
        - Marygrove BSW Visitation Program 1986 (Box 93)
        - Memos 1983-1986 (Box 93)
        - Minority Businesses 1982 (Box 93)
        - "National College of Juvenile Justice Alcohol and Drug Dependency: Youth, Families, Schools and Courts" 1984 (Box 93)
        - National Urban League 1984 (Box 93)
        - New Detroit 1983-1984 (Box 93)
        - Organization Chart 1986 (Box 93)
        - People's Law School 1986 (Box 93)
        - Personal 1985 (Box 93)
        - Personnel -- Job Descriptions 1982-1985 (Box 93)
        - Personnel Survey 1984-1985 (Box 93)
        - Program Planning Priorities Research Committee 1983-1984 (Box 93)
        - Public Issues Task Force 1982-1984, 3 folders (Box 93)
        - Research Notes circa 1983 (Box 93)
        - Research Projects (potential) 1981-1982 (Box 93)
        - Research Statistics 1987 (Box 93)
        - Senior Citizen Community Program 1983-1984 (Box 93)
        - State of Black America 1983-1985 (Box 93)
        - State of Black Detroit 1987 (Box 93)
        - Substance Abuse
          - General 1985-1986 (Box 93)
          - Harper Report 1985-1986 (Box 93)
        - Supplementary Educational Service 1986-1987 (Box 93)
        - Taxes (Detroit City and Schools) 1985 (Box 93)
        - Transportation 1985 (Box 93)